<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Demo</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string-array name="magical">

        <item>Deep magical trees murmuring breeze, carry me home\n
        微风吹过神秘的深树发出低语声，带我回家</item>

        <item>"Tell stories of hope, hope there\'s a light\n
        讲述着希望的故事，希望有一盏灯</item>

        <item>Tight energy thieves laying their wreaths outside unmarked doors\n
        拮据的能量窃贼把他们的花圈扔在了无名碑外</item>

        <item>A war is just a recourse to show that we\'re bored\n
        战争只是来证明我们无聊的一场追索</item>

        <item>Battles and wastelands, battles and wastelands in me\n
        战役与荒原，我心中的战役与荒原</item>

        <item>Magical tree where nobody grieves the island, I see\n
        神秘的树木，那里没有人为这岛屿悲伤，我知道</item>

        <item>Battles and wastelands, battles and wastelands in me\n
        战役与荒原，我心中的战役与荒原</item>

        <item>Magical tree where nobody grieves, the island I see is in me\n
        神秘的树木，那里没有人悲伤，我看见的岛屿在我心中</item>

        <item>Poor tourist you\'re lost you\'re just a cost to average man\n
        可怜的旅行者，你迷路了，你只是普通人的一个牺牲品</item>

        <item>A plan leads to a plan and you\'re told that you can\n
        一个计划导致了另一个计划，你被告知你可以</item>

        <item>You can be just who you want be what you feel, be someone real\n
        你可以成为你想成为的人，你所感受的人，做真实的自己</item>

        <item>Climb high to excess, and you\'ll be a success\n
        爬到最高点，你将成为一名成功者</item>

        <item>Battles and wastelands, battles and wastelands in me\n
        战役与荒原，我心中的战役与荒原</item>

        <item>Magical tree where nobody grieves the island, I see\n
        神秘的树木，那里没有人为这岛屿悲伤，我知道</item>

        <item>Battles and wastelands, battles and wastelands in me\n
        战役与荒原，我心中的战役与荒原</item>

        <item>Magical tree where nobody grieves, the island I see is in me\n
        神秘的树木，那里没有人悲伤，我看见的岛屿在我心中</item>

        <item>Battles and wastelands, battles and wastelands in me\n
        战役与荒原，我心中的战役与荒原</item>

        <item>Magical tree where nobody grieves the island, I see\n
        神秘的树木，那里没有人为这岛屿悲伤，我知道</item>

        <item>Battles and wastelands, battles and wastelands in me\n
        战役与荒原，我心中的战役与荒原</item>

        <item>Magical tree where nobody grieves, the island I see is in me\n
        神秘的树木，那里没有人悲伤，我看见的岛屿在我心中</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="grace">
        <item>I see you walking down the street\n
        我看到你漫步在街头</item>
        <item>I see you coming back inside\n
        我看到你回来</item>
        <item>I know you’re wondering\n
        我知道你想要了解</item>
        <item>what all this means to you\n
        这一切对你意味着什么</item>
        <item>I know you’re breaking down tonight\n
        我知道你在今夜很受伤</item>
        <item>but do you know how much it hurts\n
        但你知道（我）有多痛么</item>
        <item>to see you closing back that door\n
        当我看见你关上了那扇门</item>
        <item>I love you love you love you\n
        我爱你 爱你 爱你</item>
        <item>just the way you are\n
        只是因为 你是你</item>
        <item>Love you love you love you\n
        爱你 爱你 爱你</item>
        <item>the way you are\n
        因为 你是你</item>
        <item>There’s nothing in this world\n
        这个世界里没有什么</item>
        <item>that I would ever want\n
        是比你能回到我的怀中</item>
        <item>than to have you back in my arms.\n
        更令我想要拥有的东西</item>
        <item>I want to see you really smile\n
        我想要看到你真正的笑容</item>
        <item>Do you know it’s been a while\n
        你知道 已有一段时间</item>
        <item>Have you noticed that\n
        你有注意到么</item>
        <item>you’re far away from home\n
        你离家远了起来</item>
        <item>Do you like it where you are\n
        你喜欢这个地方么</item>
        <item>Do they treat you like a star\n
        他们把你当明星么</item>
        <item>Do they sing for you\n
        他们为你唱的歌</item>
        <item>the songs you always liked\n
        你总是喜欢么</item>
        <item>You’re scared of all the lies\n
        你害怕所有谎言</item>
        <item>All you want is a sign\n
        你需要一个目标</item>
        <item>Telling you where to go\n
        告诉你应去向何方</item>
        <item>There’s no other way to turn\n
        没有回转的余地</item>
        <item>The only lesson you learned\n
        你唯一学到的一课是</item>
        <item>is to never forget your way back home\n
        永远不要忘记回家的路</item>
        <item>I love you love you love you\n
        我爱你 爱你 爱你</item>
        <item>just the way you are\n
        只是因为 你是你</item>
        <item>Love you love you love you\n
        爱你 爱你 爱你</item>
        <item>the way you are\n
        因为 你是你</item>
        <item>There’s nothing in this world\n
        这个世界里没有什么</item>
        <item>that I would ever want\n
        是比你能回到我的怀中</item>
        <item>than to have you back in my arms.\n
        更令我想要拥有的东西</item>
        <item>Waiting for you\n
        等待着你</item>
        <item>deep in the night\n
        在深夜里</item>
        <item>to tuck you into bed\n
        哄你入眠</item>
        <item>I’m waiting for you\n
        我在等着你</item>
        <item>arms open wide\n
        张开的双臂</item>
        <item>I want to see you smile tonight\n
        今夜我想看见你的笑颜</item>
        <item>Love you love you love you\n
        爱你 爱你 爱你</item>
        <item>just the way you are\n
        只是因为 你是你</item>
        <item>Love you love you love you\n
        爱你 爱你 爱你</item>
        <item>the way you are\n
        因为 你是你</item>
        <item>There’s nothing in this world\n
        这个世界里没有什么</item>
        <item>that I would ever want\n
        是比你能回到我的怀中</item>
        <item>than to have you back in my arms.\n
        更令我想要拥有的东西</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="white">
        <item>Not sure if you know this\n
        不确定你是否清楚</item>
        <item>But when we first met\n
        当我第一次见到你</item>
        <item>I got so nervous I couldn\'t speak\n
        我紧张到话都说不清楚</item>
        <item>In that very moment\n
        在那一刻</item>
        <item>I found the one and\n
        我找到了我的唯一</item>
        <item>my life had found this missing piece\n
        终于弥补了我生命中的缺失</item>
        <item>So as long as I live I love you\n
        所以我会永远爱你</item>
        <item>Will heaven hold you\n
        会一直拥抱守护你</item>
        <item>You look so beautiful in white\n
        穿着白色婚纱的你如此美丽动人</item>
        <item>And from now to my very last breath\n
        直到我生命结束</item>
        <item>This day I\'ll cherish\n
        我都会铭记这一天</item>
        <item>You look so beautiful in white Tonight\n
        今晚穿着白色婚纱的你是如此美丽动人</item>
        <item>What we have is timeless\n
        我们拥有的是天长地久</item>
        <item>My love is endless\n
        我对你的爱是无穷无尽</item>
        <item>And with this dream I Say to the world\n
        我要把这个梦想告诉全世界</item>
        <item>You\'re my every reason you\'re all\n
        你是我全部的动力</item>
        <item>that I believe in\n
        你说的我全部相信</item>
        <item>With all my heart I mean every word\n
        每个字都由心而发</item>
        <item>So as long as I live I love you\n
        所以我会永远爱你</item>
        <item>Will heaven and hold you\n
        会一直拥抱守护你</item>
        <item>You look so beautiful in white\n
        穿着白色婚纱的你如此美丽动人</item>
        <item>And from now to my very last breath\n
        直到我生命结束</item>
        <item>This day I\'ll cherish\n
        我都会铭记这一天</item>
        <item>You look so beautiful in white Tonight\n
        今晚穿着白色婚纱的你是如此美丽动人</item>
        <item>You look so beautiful in white\n
        穿着白色婚纱的你如此美丽动人</item>
        <item>so beautiful in white\n
        穿着白色婚纱的你如此美丽动人</item>
        <item>And if our daughter is what our future holds\n
        如果我们以后生了一个女儿</item>
        <item>I hope she has your eyes\n
        我希望她也有你一般的眼睛</item>
        <item>Finds love like you and I did\n
        像你我一样遇到爱</item>
        <item>Yeah, if she falls in love and we will let her go\n
        当她坠入爱河我们就会放手</item>
        <item>I\'ll walk her down the aisle\n
        我会牵着她走过婚礼殿堂</item>
        <item>She looks so beautiful in white\n
        她穿着白色婚纱的样子一定也会很美</item>
        <item>You look so beautiful in white\n
        正如你一样</item>
        <item>So as long as I live I love you\n
        所以我会永远爱你</item>
        <item>Will heaven hold you\n
        会一直拥抱守护你</item>
        <item>You look so beautiful in white\n
        穿着白色婚纱的你如此美丽动人</item>
        <item>And from now to my very last breath\n
        直到我生命结束</item>
        <item>This day I\'ll cherish\n
        我都会铭记这一天</item>
        <item>You look so beautiful in white Tonight\n
        今晚穿着白色婚纱的你是如此美丽动人</item>
        <item>You look so beautiful in white Tonight\n
        今晚穿着白色婚纱的你是如此美丽动人</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="training_title">
        <item>Getting Started</item>
        <item>Building Your First App</item>
        <item>Supporting Different Devices</item>
        <item>Managing the Activity Lifecycle</item>
        <item>Building a Dynamic UI with Fragments</item>
        <item>Saving Data</item>
        <item>Interacting with Other Apps</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="training_content">
        <item>"Welcome to Training for Android developers. Here you\'ll find training classes that describe how to accomplish a specific task with code samples you can re-use in your app. Classes are organized into several groups you can see at the top-level of the left navigation.

The first training guides below teach you the essentials for Android app development. If you\'re a new Android app developer, you should complete each of these classes in order.

Various online video courses are also available if you\'d prefer an interactive video experience."</item>
        <item>Welcome to Android application development!

This class teaches you how to build your first Android app. You’ll learn how to create an Android project and run a debuggable version of the app. You\'ll also learn some fundamentals of Android app design, including how to build a simple user interface and handle user input.</item>
        <item>Android devices come in many shapes and sizes all around the world. With a wide range of device types, you have an opportunity to reach a huge audience with your app. In order to be as successful as possible on Android, your app needs to adapt to various device configurations. Some of the important variations that you should consider include different languages, screen sizes, and versions of the Android platform.

This class teaches you how to use basic platform features that leverage alternative resources and other features so your app can provide an optimized user experience on a variety of Android-compatible devices, using a single application package (APK).</item>
        <item>As a user navigates through, out of, and back to your app, the Activity instances in your app transition between different states in their lifecycle. For instance, when your activity starts for the first time, it comes to the foreground of the system and receives user focus. During this process, the Android system calls a series of lifecycle methods on the activity in which you set up the user interface and other components. If the user performs an action that starts another activity or switches to another app, the system calls another set of lifecycle methods on your activity as it moves into the background (where the activity is no longer visible, but the instance and its state remains intact).

Within the lifecycle callback methods, you can declare how your activity behaves when the user leaves and re-enters the activity. For example, if you\'re building a streaming video player, you might pause the video and terminate the network connection when the user switches to another app. When the user returns, you can reconnect to the network and allow the user to resume the video from the same spot.

This class explains important lifecycle callback methods that each Activity instance receives and how you can use them so your activity does what the user expects and does not consume system resources when your activity doesn\'t need them.</item>
        <item>To create a dynamic and multi-pane user interface on Android, you need to encapsulate UI components and activity behaviors into modules that you can swap into and out of your activities. You can create these modules with the Fragment class, which behaves somewhat like a nested activity that can define its own layout and manage its own lifecycle.

When a fragment specifies its own layout, it can be configured in different combinations with other fragments inside an activity to modify your layout configuration for different screen sizes (a small screen might show one fragment at a time, but a large screen can show two or more).

This class shows you how to create a dynamic user experience with fragments and optimize your app\'s user experience for devices with different screen sizes, all while continuing to support devices running versions as old as Android 1.6.</item>
        <item>Most Android apps need to save data, even if only to save information about the app state during onPause() so the user\'s progress is not lost. Most non-trivial apps also need to save user settings, and some apps must manage large amounts of information in files and databases. This class introduces you to the principal data storage options in Android, including:

Saving key-value pairs of simple data types in a shared preferences file
Saving arbitrary files in Android\'s file system
Using databases managed by SQLite</item>
        <item>An Android app typically has several activities. Each activity displays a user interface that allows the user to perform a specific task (such as view a map or take a photo). To take the user from one activity to another, your app must use an Intent to define your app\'s "intent" to do something. When you pass an Intent to the system with a method such as startActivity(), the system uses the Intent to identify and start the appropriate app component. Using intents even allows your app to start an activity that is contained in a separate app.

An Intent can be explicit in order to start a specific component (a specific Activity instance) or implicit in order to start any component that can handle the intended action (such as "capture a photo").

This class shows you how to use an Intent to perform some basic interactions with other apps, such as start another app, receive a result from that app, and make your app able to respond to intents from other apps.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_binder_demo">BinderDemo</string>


</resources>
